Next to Flume
Awesome photo협 room
Hi!
I'm Yui Kobayashi from Sakurazaka 46.
Hello!
I'm at the Kobayashi graduation concert!
Yay!
Today is January 31st, so
The first day of the concert will start later today.
I'm in front of the venue right now.
There are so many people outside the venue.
I'm sure there are a lot of people outside the venue, buying goods and so on.
I don't know...
We can only see our fans from the stage.
So today, I thought I'd get closer to you guys.
It would be nice if we could express our gratitude
I wish I could get closer to you and express my gratitude to you.
But if I go as Yui Kobayashi, it's a little bit...
That's today's show!
Panda
I'd like to wear this to meet you all.
I changed my clothes.
I wonder if I'm facing straight.
I'm a panda.
I'm going to meet you all.
Is he here?
I can't see them.
I don't know if there's anyone in there.
He's so cute.
Thank you for watching.
I'm sure we'll be hearing more and more voices.
That's definitely the vibe.
Oh!
Ooh!
Good night.
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for your time
But, edited by
Tokai Online
Thank you for your hard work
Wow you are here at this hour.
Thank you very much.
Tangerine Sports
Buy one, everybody!
Buy some Mikan Sports!
Anyone have any towels?
Who has some goods?
Which is
is
Th
Goo
Gueh fades
Ha-ha-ha
I hope you bought some goodies.
I messed up!
Can I play with it?
I made a mess!
Rumble, rattle, rattle, rattle.
It's getting cloudy
Hot
It's hot
I want to dance
Any song requests?
Good sound, good ear
I can't hear you.
Let's hear something.
What song do you like?
Can't you hear me?
I don't think he can hear you.
They're coming from inside the store.
Come here.
I'd like a Jamaican beer.
Jamaica.
I like Jamaican beer.
I'll take that.
All right.
Mmm.
There you go.
Let's go!
Let's enjoy the show!
We're back! It was so hot!
It was so hot! It was amazing to see so many Buddies fans even though it was only a few minutes before the show!
I was so surprised to see so many Buddies fans even though we hadn't arrived at the venue yet.
It was so much fun to see everyone enjoying themselves so much before the concert.
I was so happy to see that everyone had towels for the graduation concert.
By the way, I drew Rina-chan in the gacha.
By the way, I drew Rina-chan in the gacha. I hope you all drew Rina-chan in the gacha.
I wonder if some of you drew me.
I've been working with this group for about 8 and a half years.
I've also appeared on many Sakura Utaka channels, and we've had many interesting individual projects.
We have a lot of interesting individual projects as well.
I hope you will continue to watch our channel!
By the time you are watching this YouTube
We've already finished the 2nd day of the graduation concert.
I think this might be the last time for me.
Thank you so much for all the support you've given me!
I'm sure the graduation concert will be a lot of fun!
So, this is Yui Kobayashi from Sakura Utaka 46.
Thank you very much!
Thank you for watching!